Music brought them together. Time would tear them apart.
The Song of Names is a drama, music film directed by François Girard.
A man searches for his childhood best friend, a Polish violin prodigy orphaned in the
Holocaust, who vanished decades before on the night of his first public performance.
Martin Simmonds, played by Tim Roth.
Dovidl Rapoport, played by Clive Owen.
Helen Simmonds, played by Catherine McCormack.
Radio Presenter, played by Eddie Izzard.
Feinman, played by Saul Rubinek.
Dovidl 17-23, played by Jonah Hauer-King.
The Song of Names is a 2019 drama film directed by François Girard.
An adaptation of the novel of the same name by Norman Lebrecht, it stars Tim Roth and Clive Owen
as childhood friends from London whose lives have been changed by World War II.
The film was nominated for nine Canadian Screen Awards, winning five.
The film explores themes of violin, holocaust (shoah),
world war ii, jewish life, child prodigy.
The tone is emotional.